http://www.floridainsuranceschool.com/help/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Florida Insurance School, Inc collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://andybeverly.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The Florida Insurance School, Inc.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationThe Florida Insurance School, Inc may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
- To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support
needs more efficiently.
- To process payments
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to
provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except
to the extent necessary to provide the service.
- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information
they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
- To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order.
It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides
to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related
product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving
future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect
against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username,
password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication
channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share
generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information
regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the
purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services
of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not
control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices
employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their
content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy
policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites
which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The Florida Insurance School, Inc has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time.
When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently
check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal
information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy
policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and school policies.
If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following
the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this
site, please contact us at:
©2020 Andy Beverly's Florida Insurance School. - Call us: 813-962-4297 or toll free 800-634-5813
